# **Serhat Yavuzyigit**

### Senior Computer Engineering Student

**Address:** Ankara, Turkey WWW: github.com/serhatyavuzyigit

E-mail: soyavuzyigit@gmail.com

Motivated student completing Computer Engineering degree. Gained experience with two long term internships in software development. Experienced in Agile and Scrum environments. Supports team members with the project, design and programming needs. Fluent in English and Turkish. Want to contribute to the world for became a better place. Want to proof myself in big tech companies.

#### **Education**

2016-09 - Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

TOBB University Of Economics And Technology - Ankara, Turkey

• GPA: 3.02 / 4.0

• Courses Taken: Data Structures, Algorithms, Software Engineering, Computer Graphics, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning...

#### **Work Experience**

2019-01 - Software Engineer Intern

2019-04 SimBT, Ankara, Turkey

- Worked with a scrum team in defense industry software engineering project.
- Contributed to project with bugfixes, improvements and refactoring the code.
- · Gained experience with Java, Java FX and Maven.

2019-09 - Software Engineer Intern

2019-12 AYESAS

AYESAS, Ankara, Turkey

- Worked with a software engineering project team.
- Gained experience in avionics software development and Microsoft Visual Studio environment.
- Developed a tool using C++ and OT.

#### **Skills**

Software Development

Algorithms and data structures

Algorithm implementation

Java, C, C++, Python, JS, OpenGL Programming

## **Interests**

Software Development

Machine Learning / Deep Learning

Data Structures and Algorithms